<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Homegrown &#8211; Horizon Festival | Sunshine Coast</title>
	<atom:link href="/news/whats-on/category/homegrown/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Presenting 10 days and nights of visual art, music, theatre, dance, words + ideas, film and creative workshops; inspired by the stories and beauty of the Sunshine Coast.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 04:30:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Eddie Ray &#8211; Silence of the Jams</title>
		<link>/event/eddie-ray-silence-of-the-jams/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 07:05:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=1985</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Eddie Ray &#8211; Silence of the Jams is an epic independent film with an entirely original soundtrack.  Award winning artist Eddie Ray has created a comic film exploring a visual manifestation of the artist&#8217;s journey when all is lost.    In a dystopian future where the world falls into silence, and all live music has stopped, &#8230; <a href="/event/eddie-ray-silence-of-the-jams/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Eddie Ray &ndash; Silence of the Jams is an epic independent film with an entirely original soundtrack. Award winning artist Eddie Ray has created a comic film exploring a visual manifestation of the artist&rsquo;s journey when all is lost. In a dystopian future where the world falls into silence, and all live music has stopped, robots aka smartphones now rule the world. Having only ever used his trusty old...</p>
<p><a href="/event/eddie-ray-silence-of-the-jams/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sand</title>
		<link>/event/sand/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 06:52:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=1979</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The premiere of new contemporary dance work, SAND presents the interdisciplinary collaboration of Sunshine Coast based choreographer and dance artist Courtney Scheu, international visual artist Itamar Freed and collaborators.  This work exists between reality and a dream-like state, skirting the edges of surrealism and consciousness as a doorway to discover more about our relationship to &#8230; <a href="/event/sand/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The premiere of new contemporary dance work, SAND presents the interdisciplinary collaboration of Sunshine Coast based choreographer and dance artist Courtney Scheu, international visual artist Itamar Freed and collaborators. This work exists between reality and a dream-like state, skirting the edges of surrealism and consciousness as a doorway to discover more about our relationship to landscape.</p>
<p><a href="/event/sand/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Guyu and Friend Mr Pelican</title>
		<link>/event/guyu-and-friend-mr-pelican/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 06:39:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=1973</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A children’s book by Aunty Hope (Dr Hope O’Chin) that tells the Dreamtime story of a boy called Guyu and his friend, Mr Pelican. Watch a film of Aunty Hope reading the book, explore Kabi-Kabi language through the accompanying activity booklet. There will be Guyu and Friend Mr Pelican books available to take home. Guyu &#8230; <a href="/event/guyu-and-friend-mr-pelican/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A children&rsquo;s book by Aunty Hope (Dr Hope O&rsquo;Chin) that tells the Dreamtime story of a boy called Guyu and his friend, Mr Pelican. Watch a film of Aunty Hope reading the book, explore Kabi-Kabi language through the accompanying activity booklet. There will be Guyu and Friend Mr Pelican books available to take home. Guyu and Friend Mr Pelican is one of the selected Homegrown projects to appear in the...</p>
<p><a href="/event/guyu-and-friend-mr-pelican/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
