<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Wonderland Spiegeltent &#8211; Horizon Festival | Sunshine Coast</title>
	<atom:link href="/news/whats-on/category/wonderland-spiegeltent/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Presenting 10 days and nights of visual art, music, theatre, dance, words + ideas, film and creative workshops; inspired by the stories and beauty of the Sunshine Coast.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 05:04:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Circa&#8217;s Peepshow</title>
		<link>/event/circas-peepshow/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 06:42:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=3078</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Circa’s Peepshow turns cabaret on its head, literally. Join Circa as they embark on a seductive dance through the hall of mirrors that is your imagination, Circa’s Peepshow lurches from the thrillingly acrobatic to the comically playful. Expect teetering towers of balanced bodies, extreme bending, beguiling burlesque, and devilishly precarious aerials. Under the direction of &#8230; <a href="/event/circas-peepshow/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Circa&rsquo;s Peepshow turns cabaret on its head, literally. Join Circa as they embark on a seductive dance through the hall of mirrors that is your imagination, Circa&rsquo;s Peepshow lurches from the thrillingly acrobatic to the comically playful. Expect teetering towers of balanced bodies, extreme bending, beguiling burlesque, and devilishly precarious aerials. Under the direction of circus visionary Yaron...</p>
<p><a href="/event/circas-peepshow/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Critical Light: Industry Night</title>
		<link>/event/critical-light-industry-night/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 06:01:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=2341</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Public Discussion Horizon Festival sets out to ignite ideas and fuel the cultural vibrancy of our region through artistic experiences. As part of the Critical Light journey Liz Burcham, President of the SCCA, leads a discussion with Hannah Clissold, Ruby Donohoe, John Harvey and Libby Harward on the festivals value to our region. Ticket price includes &#8230; <a href="/event/critical-light-industry-night/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Horizon Festival sets out to ignite ideas and fuel the cultural vibrancy of our region through artistic experiences. As part of the Critical Light journey Liz Burcham, President of the SCCA, leads a discussion with Hannah Clissold, Ruby Donohoe, John Harvey and Libby Harward on the festivals value to our region. Ticket price includes a drink on arrival and entry to Homegrown: Eddie Ray &mdash; Silence...</p>
<p><a href="/event/critical-light-industry-night/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>horizon kids: family hours</title>
		<link>/event/horizon-kids-family-hours/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 05:41:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=2179</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Every morning the Wonderland Spiegeltent will be commandeered by kids and their keepers. Imagine a garden full of paint, glue and beanbags, and a tent full of circus, music and comedy. A space thoughtfully curated for the Coast’s little artists to have a laugh and dirty their fingernails.  Create a coastal collage in an activity &#8230; <a href="/event/horizon-kids-family-hours/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Every morning the Wonderland Spiegeltent will be commandeered by kids and their keepers. Imagine a garden full of paint, glue and beanbags, and a tent full of circus, music and comedy. A space thoughtfully curated for the Coast&rsquo;s little artists to have a laugh and dirty their fingernails. Create a coastal collage in an activity designed by The Butiner or get messy making clay animal figurines.</p>
<p><a href="/event/horizon-kids-family-hours/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What Did You Say?</title>
		<link>/event/what-did-you-say/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 22:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=1999</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On the epidermis of a tree’s leaves, microscopic pores called stomata exchange carbon dioxide for oxygen. The word ‘stomata’ comes from the Greek word ‘stoma’ meaning ‘mouth’.   What did you say? reimagines a tree’s stomata as the mouth through which the planet breathes. Using video and sound, mouths breath via amination and augmented reality.   &#8230; <a href="/event/what-did-you-say/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On the epidermis of a tree&rsquo;s leaves, microscopic pores called stomata exchange carbon dioxide for oxygen. The word &lsquo;stomata&rsquo; comes from the Greek word &lsquo;stoma&rsquo; meaning &lsquo;mouth&rsquo;. What did you say? reimagines a tree&rsquo;s stomata as the mouth through which the planet breathes. Using video and sound, mouths breath via amination and augmented reality. What did you say? responds to this strange shifting...</p>
<p><a href="/event/what-did-you-say/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Eddie Ray &#8211; Silence of the Jams</title>
		<link>/event/eddie-ray-silence-of-the-jams/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 07:05:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=1985</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Eddie Ray &#8211; Silence of the Jams is an epic independent film with an entirely original soundtrack.  Award winning artist Eddie Ray has created a comic film exploring a visual manifestation of the artist&#8217;s journey when all is lost.    In a dystopian future where the world falls into silence, and all live music has stopped, &#8230; <a href="/event/eddie-ray-silence-of-the-jams/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Eddie Ray &ndash; Silence of the Jams is an epic independent film with an entirely original soundtrack. Award winning artist Eddie Ray has created a comic film exploring a visual manifestation of the artist&rsquo;s journey when all is lost. In a dystopian future where the world falls into silence, and all live music has stopped, robots aka smartphones now rule the world. Having only ever used his trusty old...</p>
<p><a href="/event/eddie-ray-silence-of-the-jams/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Guyu and Friend Mr Pelican</title>
		<link>/event/guyu-and-friend-mr-pelican/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 06:39:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=1973</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A children’s book by Aunty Hope (Dr Hope O’Chin) that tells the Dreamtime story of a boy called Guyu and his friend, Mr Pelican. Watch a film of Aunty Hope reading the book, explore Kabi-Kabi language through the accompanying activity booklet. There will be Guyu and Friend Mr Pelican books available to take home. Guyu &#8230; <a href="/event/guyu-and-friend-mr-pelican/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A children&rsquo;s book by Aunty Hope (Dr Hope O&rsquo;Chin) that tells the Dreamtime story of a boy called Guyu and his friend, Mr Pelican. Watch a film of Aunty Hope reading the book, explore Kabi-Kabi language through the accompanying activity booklet. There will be Guyu and Friend Mr Pelican books available to take home. Guyu and Friend Mr Pelican is one of the selected Homegrown projects to appear in the...</p>
<p><a href="/event/guyu-and-friend-mr-pelican/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Creative Bubs with New Dreaming Art</title>
		<link>/event/creative-bubs-with-new-dreaming-art/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 05:09:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=1936</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A chance for parents, grandparents, aunties and uncles to connect with their youngest ones. New Dreaming Art and Didgeridoo Music Therapy share their cultural history in a safe and creative space, teaching you and bub to make art that tells your own family’s story.  Enjoy the beautiful sounds of the Yidaki (didgeridoo) with Caleb while &#8230; <a href="/event/creative-bubs-with-new-dreaming-art/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A chance for parents, grandparents, aunties and uncles to connect with their youngest ones. New Dreaming Art and Didgeridoo Music Therapy share their cultural history in a safe and creative space, teaching you and bub to make art that tells your own family&rsquo;s story. Enjoy the beautiful sounds of the Yidaki (didgeridoo) with Caleb while expressing yourself through art with Nikita.</p>
<p><a href="/event/creative-bubs-with-new-dreaming-art/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Creative Play with Wildlings Forest School</title>
		<link>/event/creative-play-with-wildlings-forest-school/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 04:59:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=1930</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[An opportunity for the youngest artists of the Sunshine Coast to get creative, with a range of 3-hour workshops led by the experts in outdoor play — Wildlings Forest School.  Thu 1 Sep / Painting with Jandamarra Fri 2 Sep / Hapazome: The Art of Flower Pressing Sat 3 Sep / Clay Play Sun 4 Sep / &#8230; <a href="/event/creative-play-with-wildlings-forest-school/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An opportunity for the youngest artists of the Sunshine Coast to get creative, with a range of 3-hour workshops led by the experts in outdoor play &mdash; Wildlings Forest School. Thu 1 Sep / Painting with Jandamarra Fri 2 Sep / Hapazome: The Art of Flower Pressing Sat 3 Sep / Clay Play Sun 4 Sep / Making Mini-Boats This event is recommended for children aged 4&ndash;12. Image credits: Samantha Laine Smith...</p>
<p><a href="/event/creative-play-with-wildlings-forest-school/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>HOLY BIN AMOLEY!</title>
		<link>/event/holy-bin-amoley/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 04:47:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=1924</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[HOLY BIN AMOLEY! is a comedy sketch show brought to you by three ridiculous, bin-loving sillies. Meet bin-vestigators catching out non-recycling nannies, boogie with the bin chickens, witness the world&#8217;s first Bin Doggy Show, and so much more!  This show is the ultimate guide on how to become your best bin self! It’s a show &#8230; <a href="/event/holy-bin-amoley/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>HOLY BIN AMOLEY! is a comedy sketch show brought to you by three ridiculous, bin-loving sillies. Meet bin-vestigators catching out non-recycling nannies, boogie with the bin chickens, witness the world&rsquo;s first Bin Doggy Show, and so much more! This show is the ultimate guide on how to become your best bin self! It&rsquo;s a show for the whole family with a focus on working out where each piece of...</p>
<p><a href="/event/holy-bin-amoley/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Babushka in Right to Party</title>
		<link>/event/babushka-kids-right-to-party/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 03:56:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=1919</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[School of Rock meets Beastie Boys and the Spice Girls in this rebellious party playlist.  A high energy cabaret for kids, featuring rebellious music, vocal acrobatics and a whole lotta mischief &#8211; spike your mohawk and fight for your right to party!   After performing to rapturous applause at Adelaide Fringe Festival and Queensland Cabaret Festival, &#8230; <a href="/event/babushka-kids-right-to-party/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>School of Rock meets Beastie Boys and the Spice Girls in this rebellious party playlist. A high energy cabaret for kids, featuring rebellious music, vocal acrobatics and a whole lotta mischief &ndash; spike your mohawk and fight for your right to party! After performing to rapturous applause at Adelaide Fringe Festival and Queensland Cabaret Festival, award-winning group Babushka has cooked up their...</p>
<p><a href="/event/babushka-kids-right-to-party/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
