<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Free &#8211; Horizon Festival | Sunshine Coast</title>
	<atom:link href="/news/whats-on/category/free/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Presenting 10 days and nights of visual art, music, theatre, dance, words + ideas, film and creative workshops; inspired by the stories and beauty of the Sunshine Coast.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 22:51:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>horizon kids: family hours</title>
		<link>/event/horizon-kids-family-hours/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 05:41:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=2179</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Every morning the Wonderland Spiegeltent will be commandeered by kids and their keepers. Imagine a garden full of paint, glue and beanbags, and a tent full of circus, music and comedy. A space thoughtfully curated for the Coast’s little artists to have a laugh and dirty their fingernails.  Create a coastal collage in an activity &#8230; <a href="/event/horizon-kids-family-hours/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Every morning the Wonderland Spiegeltent will be commandeered by kids and their keepers. Imagine a garden full of paint, glue and beanbags, and a tent full of circus, music and comedy. A space thoughtfully curated for the Coast&rsquo;s little artists to have a laugh and dirty their fingernails. Create a coastal collage in an activity designed by The Butiner or get messy making clay animal figurines.</p>
<p><a href="/event/horizon-kids-family-hours/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Risograph printing with the Sunshine Press</title>
		<link>/event/risography-with-the-sunshine-press/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 04:18:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=2141</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Attention: Talented High School Visual Artists. Horizon Festival and The Sunshine Press are partnering to offer a free, full day workshop in the art of Risograph Printing.  The Sunshine Press are offering a small group of young Sunshine Coast Visual Artists the opportunity to learn an old art form that’s finding new life — Risograph &#8230; <a href="/event/risography-with-the-sunshine-press/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Attention: Talented High School Visual Artists. Horizon Festival and The Sunshine Press are partnering to offer a free, full day workshop in the art of Risograph Printing. The Sunshine Press are offering a small group of young Sunshine Coast Visual Artists the opportunity to learn an old art form that&rsquo;s finding new life &mdash; Risograph Printing. Applications for high school-aged artists are now open.</p>
<p><a href="/event/risography-with-the-sunshine-press/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Sinkers</title>
		<link>/event/the-sinkers/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 01:24:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=2072</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Presented by Lara Fischel Chisholm from the Wet Hot Beauties and captained by Ruby Donohoe. Join Ruby Donohoe Club Captain and Lara Fischel Chisholm (Wet Hot Beauties, NZ) as they lead The Sinkers; the Sunshine Coast’s most underwhelming synchronised swimming club. This fun, 20 minute pop-up show welcomes everyone, and aims to connect the coast &#8230; <a href="/event/the-sinkers/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Presented by Lara Fischel Chisholm from the Wet Hot Beauties and captained by Ruby Donohoe. Join Ruby Donohoe Club Captain and Lara Fischel Chisholm (Wet Hot Beauties, NZ) as they lead The Sinkers; the Sunshine Coast&rsquo;s most underwhelming synchronised swimming club. This fun, 20 minute pop-up show welcomes everyone, and aims to connect the coast through humour and refreshing entertainment.</p>
<p><a href="/event/the-sinkers/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Looks Like A Tourist</title>
		<link>/event/looks-like-a-tourist/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 01:01:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=2063</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bringing to life our most iconic destinations, LOOKS LIKE A TOURIST is a visual spectacle that saturates the landscape bringing our attention to the complexities of being a visitor in a new place.  Unidentified strangers dressed in inflatable orange suits saturate the landscape, bringing our attention to the complexities of being a visitor in a &#8230; <a href="/event/looks-like-a-tourist/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bringing to life our most iconic destinations, LOOKS LIKE A TOURIST is a visual spectacle that saturates the landscape bringing our attention to the complexities of being a visitor in a new place. Unidentified strangers dressed in inflatable orange suits saturate the landscape, bringing our attention to the complexities of being a visitor in a new place. Their movements shift the romanticism of...</p>
<p><a href="/event/looks-like-a-tourist/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Country Is Calling</title>
		<link>/event/country-is-calling/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 00:40:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=2058</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Country is Calling is a visual art exhibition that celebrates the work and stories of the Jinibara people; the Traditional Custodians of the mountains, valleys and hinterlands of the Sunshine Coast.    Curated by prominent Jinibara artist Jason Murphy, the exhibition explores the intricate connection between people and place. The four featured Jinibara artists — Jason &#8230; <a href="/event/country-is-calling/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Country is Calling is a visual art exhibition that celebrates the work and stories of the Jinibara people; the Traditional Custodians of the mountains, valleys and hinterlands of the Sunshine Coast. Curated by prominent Jinibara artist Jason Murphy, the exhibition explores the intricate connection between people and place. The four featured Jinibara artists &mdash; Jason Murphy, Caitlin Murphy...</p>
<p><a href="/event/country-is-calling/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sunshine Coast Art Prize</title>
		<link>/event/sunshine-coast-art-prize-scap/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 00:26:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=2050</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Sunshine Coast Art Prize is one of the most dynamic and prestigious visual arts awards in Australia. Now in its 17th year, this premier art event attracts entries from established and emerging artists from across the nation. In 2022, we will have Ellie Buttrose, Curator, Contemporary Australian Art, QAGOMA, joining us as guest judge &#8230; <a href="/event/sunshine-coast-art-prize-scap/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Sunshine Coast Art Prize is one of the most dynamic and prestigious visual arts awards in Australia. Now in its 17th year, this premier art event attracts entries from established and emerging artists from across the nation. In 2022, we will have Ellie Buttrose, Curator, Contemporary Australian Art, QAGOMA, joining us as guest judge for the judged prize categories (Major Prize...</p>
<p><a href="/event/sunshine-coast-art-prize-scap/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Kabi Kabi Connections</title>
		<link>/event/kabi-kabi-connections-2/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 00:12:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=2037</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Kabi Kabi Connections is the union between time immemorial and the ephemeral, where sacred ways of knowing and being meet new technologies and the natural environment.    Curated by knowledge keeper and artist, Helena Gulash and interdisciplinary artist James Muller, this immersive and meditative work illuminates the waters of the Maroochy River with the work &#8230; <a href="/event/kabi-kabi-connections-2/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Kabi Kabi Connections is the union between time immemorial and the ephemeral, where sacred ways of knowing and being meet new technologies and the natural environment. Curated by knowledge keeper and artist, Helena Gulash and interdisciplinary artist James Muller, this immersive and meditative work illuminates the waters of the Maroochy River with the work of Traditional Custodians and visual arts...</p>
<p><a href="/event/kabi-kabi-connections-2/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Listen more not spoken for</title>
		<link>/event/listen-more-not-spoken-for/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 23:58:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=2033</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Have you ever had a conversation with country? If you listen carefully, can you hear her way of speaking with us? Immerse in the sounds of children and country hearing each other. These listening walks have been created by a team of Jarjums (Indigenous children) in collaboration with Quandamooka artist Libby Harward, their older siblings &#8230; <a href="/event/listen-more-not-spoken-for/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Have you ever had a conversation with country? If you listen carefully, can you hear her way of speaking with us? Immerse in the sounds of children and country hearing each other. These listening walks have been created by a team of Jarjums (Indigenous children) in collaboration with Quandamooka artist Libby Harward, their older siblings and our Mother Earth. The Jarjums and Libby will also...</p>
<p><a href="/event/listen-more-not-spoken-for/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Peter Hudson: The Mystery of Being Here</title>
		<link>/event/peter-hudson-the-mystery-of-being-here/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 23:44:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=2025</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Mystery of Being Here The Mystery of Being Here is the largest career survey of Sunshine Coast-based artist, Peter Hudson. Since the 1990s, Hudson has explored aspects of the natural world through painting and drawing. The landscape has been a constant for Hudson, particularly the Glass House Mountains and hinterland around Maleny where he resides. &#8230; <a href="/event/peter-hudson-the-mystery-of-being-here/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Mystery of Being Here The Mystery of Being Here is the largest career survey of Sunshine Coast-based artist, Peter Hudson. Since the 1990s, Hudson has explored aspects of the natural world through painting and drawing. The landscape has been a constant for Hudson, particularly the Glass House Mountains and hinterland around Maleny where he resides. The moon, ocean, fish, birds and snakes also...</p>
<p><a href="/event/peter-hudson-the-mystery-of-being-here/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The C Word</title>
		<link>/event/the-c-word/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 23:26:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=2018</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Culture, Crisis, Comfort, Confusion, Cloak, Concealment, Cocoon, C…  The C Word has as many understandings as the individuals who encounter it. Kim Schoenberger takes this ambiguity and melds it into forms and structures that interrogate the societal stasis wrought by a global phenomenon.  In a reflection on our contemporary zeitgeist, The C Word investigates the &#8230; <a href="/event/the-c-word/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Culture, Crisis, Comfort, Confusion, Cloak, Concealment, Cocoon, C&hellip; The C Word has as many understandings as the individuals who encounter it. Kim Schoenberger takes this ambiguity and melds it into forms and structures that interrogate the societal stasis wrought by a global phenomenon. In a reflection on our contemporary zeitgeist, The C Word investigates the prominence of remembered fears...</p>
<p><a href="/event/the-c-word/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
