<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Performance &#8211; Horizon Festival | Sunshine Coast</title>
	<atom:link href="/news/whats-on/category/performance/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Presenting 10 days and nights of visual art, music, theatre, dance, words + ideas, film and creative workshops; inspired by the stories and beauty of the Sunshine Coast.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 04:30:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Circa&#8217;s Peepshow</title>
		<link>/event/circas-peepshow/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 06:42:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=3078</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Circa’s Peepshow turns cabaret on its head, literally. Join Circa as they embark on a seductive dance through the hall of mirrors that is your imagination, Circa’s Peepshow lurches from the thrillingly acrobatic to the comically playful. Expect teetering towers of balanced bodies, extreme bending, beguiling burlesque, and devilishly precarious aerials. Under the direction of &#8230; <a href="/event/circas-peepshow/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Circa&rsquo;s Peepshow turns cabaret on its head, literally. Join Circa as they embark on a seductive dance through the hall of mirrors that is your imagination, Circa&rsquo;s Peepshow lurches from the thrillingly acrobatic to the comically playful. Expect teetering towers of balanced bodies, extreme bending, beguiling burlesque, and devilishly precarious aerials. Under the direction of circus visionary Yaron...</p>
<p><a href="/event/circas-peepshow/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Playlist</title>
		<link>/event/the-playlist/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 02:49:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=2110</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Favourite songs underscoring fabulous stories.   Stories of people and their connection to Coolum. Joyous, Heartbreaking, Mischievous, Hilarious. Music to match the sentiment of the story. Sentiment indivisible from its musical score. The Playlist is a place-based performance work centred on the songs of Coolum and the stories that connect them to the community. Throughout 2022, &#8230; <a href="/event/the-playlist/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Favourite songs underscoring fabulous stories. Stories of people and their connection to Coolum. Joyous, Heartbreaking, Mischievous, Hilarious. Music to match the sentiment of the story. Sentiment indivisible from its musical score. The Playlist is a place-based performance work centred on the songs of Coolum and the stories that connect them to the community. Throughout 2022...</p>
<p><a href="/event/the-playlist/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Medicament for your Predicament</title>
		<link>/event/medicament-for-your-predicament/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 02:05:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=2084</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Medicament For Your Predicament is an experimental pharmacy of political medicines. From antidotes, to ire and diuretics for disillusionment, to cures for capitalism — tonics, salves, gargles and powders for our soluble and insoluble bodies. Take part and contribute to this project in OPEN LAB! a hands-on workshop to diagnose matters close to the heart and formulate your &#8230; <a href="/event/medicament-for-your-predicament/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Medicament For Your Predicament is an experimental pharmacy of political medicines. From antidotes, to ire and diuretics for disillusionment, to cures for capitalism &mdash; tonics, salves, gargles and powders for our soluble and insoluble bodies. Take part and contribute to this project in OPEN LAB! a hands-on workshop to diagnose matters close to the heart and formulate your very own remedy and recipe...</p>
<p><a href="/event/medicament-for-your-predicament/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Sinkers</title>
		<link>/event/the-sinkers/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 01:24:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=2072</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Presented by Lara Fischel Chisholm from the Wet Hot Beauties and captained by Ruby Donohoe. Join Ruby Donohoe Club Captain and Lara Fischel Chisholm (Wet Hot Beauties, NZ) as they lead The Sinkers; the Sunshine Coast’s most underwhelming synchronised swimming club. This fun, 20 minute pop-up show welcomes everyone, and aims to connect the coast &#8230; <a href="/event/the-sinkers/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Presented by Lara Fischel Chisholm from the Wet Hot Beauties and captained by Ruby Donohoe. Join Ruby Donohoe Club Captain and Lara Fischel Chisholm (Wet Hot Beauties, NZ) as they lead The Sinkers; the Sunshine Coast&rsquo;s most underwhelming synchronised swimming club. This fun, 20 minute pop-up show welcomes everyone, and aims to connect the coast through humour and refreshing entertainment.</p>
<p><a href="/event/the-sinkers/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Looks Like A Tourist</title>
		<link>/event/looks-like-a-tourist/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 01:01:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=2063</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bringing to life our most iconic destinations, LOOKS LIKE A TOURIST is a visual spectacle that saturates the landscape bringing our attention to the complexities of being a visitor in a new place.  Unidentified strangers dressed in inflatable orange suits saturate the landscape, bringing our attention to the complexities of being a visitor in a &#8230; <a href="/event/looks-like-a-tourist/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bringing to life our most iconic destinations, LOOKS LIKE A TOURIST is a visual spectacle that saturates the landscape bringing our attention to the complexities of being a visitor in a new place. Unidentified strangers dressed in inflatable orange suits saturate the landscape, bringing our attention to the complexities of being a visitor in a new place. Their movements shift the romanticism of...</p>
<p><a href="/event/looks-like-a-tourist/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Eddie Ray &#8211; Silence of the Jams</title>
		<link>/event/eddie-ray-silence-of-the-jams/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 07:05:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=1985</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Eddie Ray &#8211; Silence of the Jams is an epic independent film with an entirely original soundtrack.  Award winning artist Eddie Ray has created a comic film exploring a visual manifestation of the artist&#8217;s journey when all is lost.    In a dystopian future where the world falls into silence, and all live music has stopped, &#8230; <a href="/event/eddie-ray-silence-of-the-jams/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Eddie Ray &ndash; Silence of the Jams is an epic independent film with an entirely original soundtrack. Award winning artist Eddie Ray has created a comic film exploring a visual manifestation of the artist&rsquo;s journey when all is lost. In a dystopian future where the world falls into silence, and all live music has stopped, robots aka smartphones now rule the world. Having only ever used his trusty old...</p>
<p><a href="/event/eddie-ray-silence-of-the-jams/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sand</title>
		<link>/event/sand/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 06:52:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=1979</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The premiere of new contemporary dance work, SAND presents the interdisciplinary collaboration of Sunshine Coast based choreographer and dance artist Courtney Scheu, international visual artist Itamar Freed and collaborators.  This work exists between reality and a dream-like state, skirting the edges of surrealism and consciousness as a doorway to discover more about our relationship to &#8230; <a href="/event/sand/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The premiere of new contemporary dance work, SAND presents the interdisciplinary collaboration of Sunshine Coast based choreographer and dance artist Courtney Scheu, international visual artist Itamar Freed and collaborators. This work exists between reality and a dream-like state, skirting the edges of surrealism and consciousness as a doorway to discover more about our relationship to landscape.</p>
<p><a href="/event/sand/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>HOLY BIN AMOLEY!</title>
		<link>/event/holy-bin-amoley/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 04:47:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=1924</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[HOLY BIN AMOLEY! is a comedy sketch show brought to you by three ridiculous, bin-loving sillies. Meet bin-vestigators catching out non-recycling nannies, boogie with the bin chickens, witness the world&#8217;s first Bin Doggy Show, and so much more!  This show is the ultimate guide on how to become your best bin self! It’s a show &#8230; <a href="/event/holy-bin-amoley/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>HOLY BIN AMOLEY! is a comedy sketch show brought to you by three ridiculous, bin-loving sillies. Meet bin-vestigators catching out non-recycling nannies, boogie with the bin chickens, witness the world&rsquo;s first Bin Doggy Show, and so much more! This show is the ultimate guide on how to become your best bin self! It&rsquo;s a show for the whole family with a focus on working out where each piece of...</p>
<p><a href="/event/holy-bin-amoley/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Circus Wonderland – A Neverland Adventure</title>
		<link>/event/circus-wonderland-a-neverland-adventure/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 03:34:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=1906</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Audiences young and the young at heart will be all smiles enjoying the spell-binding magic of Circus Wonderland. Fun for the whole family as the adventures of Peter Pan, Tinkerbell and the Pirates come to life with a fun-filled enchanting circus adventure for the whole family.  A fantasy wonderland of family entertainment you will never &#8230; <a href="/event/circus-wonderland-a-neverland-adventure/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Audiences young and the young at heart will be all smiles enjoying the spell-binding magic of Circus Wonderland. Fun for the whole family as the adventures of Peter Pan, Tinkerbell and the Pirates come to life with a fun-filled enchanting circus adventure for the whole family. A fantasy wonderland of family entertainment you will never forget! Starring an amazing world class cast of acrobatic...</p>
<p><a href="/event/circus-wonderland-a-neverland-adventure/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Common People Dance PARTY: Sunshine Coast Rally</title>
		<link>/event/common-people-dance-party-sunshine-coast-rally/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 03:22:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=1899</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[All year, the Common People Dance Project has been working with people of all ages and abilities to shape a series of over-the-top dance routines to some of the greatest hits of the &#8217;80s and &#8217;90s in homage to the legendary Rock Eisteddfods of decades past.  The Sunshine Coast is about to compete in a &#8230; <a href="/event/common-people-dance-party-sunshine-coast-rally/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>All year, the Common People Dance Project has been working with people of all ages and abilities to shape a series of over-the-top dance routines to some of the greatest hits of the &rsquo;80s and &rsquo;90s in homage to the legendary Rock Eisteddfods of decades past. The Sunshine Coast is about to compete in a storm of sequins, sweat and spandex in one mighty dance- battle-royale, against teams of dancers...</p>
<p><a href="/event/common-people-dance-party-sunshine-coast-rally/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
