<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Workshops &#8211; Horizon Festival | Sunshine Coast</title>
	<atom:link href="/news/whats-on/category/workshops/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Presenting 10 days and nights of visual art, music, theatre, dance, words + ideas, film and creative workshops; inspired by the stories and beauty of the Sunshine Coast.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 05:04:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Storytellers Festival + Workshops</title>
		<link>/event/storytellers-festival-workshops/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 04:17:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=3050</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Sunshine Coast Libraries is hosting the coast&#8217;s biggest combined book launch at Beerwah. The Sunshine Coast is home to an abundance of exceptional literary talent. Libraries are bringing together writers, readers and creatives to share our love of books and support our local authors.  The Storytellers Festival 2022 offers the opportunity to meet and mingle &#8230; <a href="/event/storytellers-festival-workshops/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Sunshine Coast Libraries is hosting the coast&rsquo;s biggest combined book launch at Beerwah. The Sunshine Coast is home to an abundance of exceptional literary talent. Libraries are bringing together writers, readers and creatives to share our love of books and support our local authors. The Storytellers Festival 2022 offers the opportunity to meet and mingle with successful local authors...</p>
<p><a href="/event/storytellers-festival-workshops/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>horizon kids: family hours</title>
		<link>/event/horizon-kids-family-hours/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 05:41:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=2179</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Every morning the Wonderland Spiegeltent will be commandeered by kids and their keepers. Imagine a garden full of paint, glue and beanbags, and a tent full of circus, music and comedy. A space thoughtfully curated for the Coast’s little artists to have a laugh and dirty their fingernails.  Create a coastal collage in an activity &#8230; <a href="/event/horizon-kids-family-hours/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Every morning the Wonderland Spiegeltent will be commandeered by kids and their keepers. Imagine a garden full of paint, glue and beanbags, and a tent full of circus, music and comedy. A space thoughtfully curated for the Coast&rsquo;s little artists to have a laugh and dirty their fingernails. Create a coastal collage in an activity designed by The Butiner or get messy making clay animal figurines.</p>
<p><a href="/event/horizon-kids-family-hours/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>ReCONNECT</title>
		<link>/event/reconnect/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 04:39:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=2153</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[To accompany her exhibition The C Word, Kim Schoenberger will be hosting a two-hour experimental workshop that explores the notion of the Self through personal identity and art making. Beginning with a series of short hands-on loosening up exercises, this workshop aims to unlock pathways into the realm of creativity through the use of collage, textiles and wire armature &#8230; <a href="/event/reconnect/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>To accompany her exhibition The C Word, Kim Schoenberger will be hosting a two-hour experimental workshop that explores the notion of the Self through personal identity and art making. Beginning with a series of short hands-on loosening up exercises, this workshop aims to unlock pathways into the realm of creativity through the use of collage, textiles and wire armature sculpture.</p>
<p><a href="/event/reconnect/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Clay with Robert Natoli</title>
		<link>/event/clay-with-robert-natoli/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 04:31:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=2146</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Join expert artist, potter, painter and educator, Robert Natoli for a hands-on ceramics workshop and conversation. Bring your own wine, dig your hands into some clay and hear first-hand about Robert’s artistic process. Guests will get an expert, uniquely personal lesson in ceramic hand-building techniques from one of the Coast’s leading artists and educators at one of his resident &#8230; <a href="/event/clay-with-robert-natoli/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Join expert artist, potter, painter and educator, Robert Natoli for a hands-on ceramics workshop and conversation. Bring your own wine, dig your hands into some clay and hear first-hand about Robert&rsquo;s artistic process. Guests will get an expert, uniquely personal lesson in ceramic hand-building techniques from one of the Coast&rsquo;s leading artists and educators at one of his resident studios &ndash; The...</p>
<p><a href="/event/clay-with-robert-natoli/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Risograph printing with the Sunshine Press</title>
		<link>/event/risography-with-the-sunshine-press/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 04:18:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=2141</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Attention: Talented High School Visual Artists. Horizon Festival and The Sunshine Press are partnering to offer a free, full day workshop in the art of Risograph Printing.  The Sunshine Press are offering a small group of young Sunshine Coast Visual Artists the opportunity to learn an old art form that’s finding new life — Risograph &#8230; <a href="/event/risography-with-the-sunshine-press/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Attention: Talented High School Visual Artists. Horizon Festival and The Sunshine Press are partnering to offer a free, full day workshop in the art of Risograph Printing. The Sunshine Press are offering a small group of young Sunshine Coast Visual Artists the opportunity to learn an old art form that&rsquo;s finding new life &mdash; Risograph Printing. Applications for high school-aged artists are now open.</p>
<p><a href="/event/risography-with-the-sunshine-press/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Collage with The Butiner</title>
		<link>/event/collage-with-the-butiner/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 04:05:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=2134</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Butiner self-describes as a collage artist, flower lover, and story teller. Bring your own wine, as you create and learn with The Butiner, Peta O’Hara, in her studio, and hear about her process in this rare collage workshop.  Using identical imagery and materials, guests will create deeply originally collage postcards inspired by their own &#8230; <a href="/event/collage-with-the-butiner/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Butiner self-describes as a collage artist, flower lover, and story teller. Bring your own wine, as you create and learn with The Butiner, Peta O&rsquo;Hara, in her studio, and hear about her process in this rare collage workshop. Using identical imagery and materials, guests will create deeply originally collage postcards inspired by their own connection to their homes, in a uniquely personal...</p>
<p><a href="/event/collage-with-the-butiner/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Medicament for your Predicament</title>
		<link>/event/medicament-for-your-predicament/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 02:05:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=2084</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Medicament For Your Predicament is an experimental pharmacy of political medicines. From antidotes, to ire and diuretics for disillusionment, to cures for capitalism — tonics, salves, gargles and powders for our soluble and insoluble bodies. Take part and contribute to this project in OPEN LAB! a hands-on workshop to diagnose matters close to the heart and formulate your &#8230; <a href="/event/medicament-for-your-predicament/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Medicament For Your Predicament is an experimental pharmacy of political medicines. From antidotes, to ire and diuretics for disillusionment, to cures for capitalism &mdash; tonics, salves, gargles and powders for our soluble and insoluble bodies. Take part and contribute to this project in OPEN LAB! a hands-on workshop to diagnose matters close to the heart and formulate your very own remedy and recipe...</p>
<p><a href="/event/medicament-for-your-predicament/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Creative Bubs with New Dreaming Art</title>
		<link>/event/creative-bubs-with-new-dreaming-art/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 05:09:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=1936</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A chance for parents, grandparents, aunties and uncles to connect with their youngest ones. New Dreaming Art and Didgeridoo Music Therapy share their cultural history in a safe and creative space, teaching you and bub to make art that tells your own family’s story.  Enjoy the beautiful sounds of the Yidaki (didgeridoo) with Caleb while &#8230; <a href="/event/creative-bubs-with-new-dreaming-art/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A chance for parents, grandparents, aunties and uncles to connect with their youngest ones. New Dreaming Art and Didgeridoo Music Therapy share their cultural history in a safe and creative space, teaching you and bub to make art that tells your own family&rsquo;s story. Enjoy the beautiful sounds of the Yidaki (didgeridoo) with Caleb while expressing yourself through art with Nikita.</p>
<p><a href="/event/creative-bubs-with-new-dreaming-art/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Creative Play with Wildlings Forest School</title>
		<link>/event/creative-play-with-wildlings-forest-school/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 04:59:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=1930</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[An opportunity for the youngest artists of the Sunshine Coast to get creative, with a range of 3-hour workshops led by the experts in outdoor play — Wildlings Forest School.  Thu 1 Sep / Painting with Jandamarra Fri 2 Sep / Hapazome: The Art of Flower Pressing Sat 3 Sep / Clay Play Sun 4 Sep / &#8230; <a href="/event/creative-play-with-wildlings-forest-school/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An opportunity for the youngest artists of the Sunshine Coast to get creative, with a range of 3-hour workshops led by the experts in outdoor play &mdash; Wildlings Forest School. Thu 1 Sep / Painting with Jandamarra Fri 2 Sep / Hapazome: The Art of Flower Pressing Sat 3 Sep / Clay Play Sun 4 Sep / Making Mini-Boats This event is recommended for children aged 4&ndash;12. Image credits: Samantha Laine Smith...</p>
<p><a href="/event/creative-play-with-wildlings-forest-school/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
