<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Music &#8211; Horizon Festival | Sunshine Coast</title>
	<atom:link href="/news/whats-on/category/music/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Presenting 10 days and nights of visual art, music, theatre, dance, words + ideas, film and creative workshops; inspired by the stories and beauty of the Sunshine Coast.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2022 03:45:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>The Playlist</title>
		<link>/event/the-playlist/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 02:49:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=2110</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Favourite songs underscoring fabulous stories.   Stories of people and their connection to Coolum. Joyous, Heartbreaking, Mischievous, Hilarious. Music to match the sentiment of the story. Sentiment indivisible from its musical score. The Playlist is a place-based performance work centred on the songs of Coolum and the stories that connect them to the community. Throughout 2022, &#8230; <a href="/event/the-playlist/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Favourite songs underscoring fabulous stories. Stories of people and their connection to Coolum. Joyous, Heartbreaking, Mischievous, Hilarious. Music to match the sentiment of the story. Sentiment indivisible from its musical score. The Playlist is a place-based performance work centred on the songs of Coolum and the stories that connect them to the community. Throughout 2022...</p>
<p><a href="/event/the-playlist/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Eddie Ray &#8211; Silence of the Jams</title>
		<link>/event/eddie-ray-silence-of-the-jams/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 07:05:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=1985</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Eddie Ray &#8211; Silence of the Jams is an epic independent film with an entirely original soundtrack.  Award winning artist Eddie Ray has created a comic film exploring a visual manifestation of the artist&#8217;s journey when all is lost.    In a dystopian future where the world falls into silence, and all live music has stopped, &#8230; <a href="/event/eddie-ray-silence-of-the-jams/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Eddie Ray &ndash; Silence of the Jams is an epic independent film with an entirely original soundtrack. Award winning artist Eddie Ray has created a comic film exploring a visual manifestation of the artist&rsquo;s journey when all is lost. In a dystopian future where the world falls into silence, and all live music has stopped, robots aka smartphones now rule the world. Having only ever used his trusty old...</p>
<p><a href="/event/eddie-ray-silence-of-the-jams/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Open Air: Yirinda</title>
		<link>/event/open-air-yirinda/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 06:19:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=1968</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[From hidden lakes to ocean-scapes, Open Air is a vivid collision of music and place. Fast becoming an essential experience for locals and visitors alike, this intimate outdoor concert series features some of Australia’s most innovative musicians set against the Sunshine Coast’s spectacular natural environment.  Butchulla Songman Fred Leone and internationally acclaimed composer/multi-instrumentalist Samuel Pankhurst &#8230; <a href="/event/open-air-yirinda/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From hidden lakes to ocean-scapes, Open Air is a vivid collision of music and place. Fast becoming an essential experience for locals and visitors alike, this intimate outdoor concert series features some of Australia&rsquo;s most innovative musicians set against the Sunshine Coast&rsquo;s spectacular natural environment. Butchulla Songman Fred Leone and internationally acclaimed composer/</p>
<p><a href="/event/open-air-yirinda/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Open Air: Cloe Terare</title>
		<link>/event/open-air-cloe-terrare/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 06:09:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=1962</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[From hidden lakes to ocean-scapes, Open Air is a vivid collision of music and place. Fast becoming an essential experience for locals and visitors alike, this intimate outdoor concert series features some of Australia’s most innovative musicians set against the Sunshine Coast’s spectacular natural environment.  Her Debut EP Burn Book (2018-2021) spawned singles that were &#8230; <a href="/event/open-air-cloe-terrare/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From hidden lakes to ocean-scapes, Open Air is a vivid collision of music and place. Fast becoming an essential experience for locals and visitors alike, this intimate outdoor concert series features some of Australia&rsquo;s most innovative musicians set against the Sunshine Coast&rsquo;s spectacular natural environment. Her Debut EP Burn Book (2018-2021) spawned singles that were added to Triple J...</p>
<p><a href="/event/open-air-cloe-terrare/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Songs of GAIA</title>
		<link>/event/songs-of-gaia/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 05:50:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=1953</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[IMPORTANT INFORMATON  Due to the inclement weather and technical nature of Songs of Gaia, in close consultation with the artists we have made the difficult decision to move the event indoors. Songs of Gaia will now take place at the Coolum Civic Centre, 2-4 Park Street Coolum. You are invited to BYO picnic and drinks &#8230; <a href="/event/songs-of-gaia/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>IMPORTANT INFORMATON Due to the inclement weather and technical nature of Songs of Gaia, in close consultation with the artists we have made the difficult decision to move the event indoors. Songs of Gaia will now take place at the Coolum Civic Centre, 2-4 Park Street Coolum. You are invited to BYO picnic and drinks to this performance. A coffee van will also be available at the venue.</p>
<p><a href="/event/songs-of-gaia/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Open Air: Saturdaze with Blak Social</title>
		<link>/event/open-air-saturdaze-with-blak-social/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 05:38:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=1947</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Celebrating several of the Sunshine Coast’s regional hinterland towns. Open Air presents a Hinterland series of live music performances featuring some of Australia’s most loved musicians. First Nations Artists bring good vibes and big ancestor energy to all they create. Leaders in the cultural resurgence of Indigenous peoples across South East Queensland, Blak Social has curated &#8230; <a href="/event/open-air-saturdaze-with-blak-social/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Celebrating several of the Sunshine Coast&rsquo;s regional hinterland towns. Open Air presents a Hinterland series of live music performances featuring some of Australia&rsquo;s most loved musicians. First Nations Artists bring good vibes and big ancestor energy to all they create. Leaders in the cultural resurgence of Indigenous peoples across South East Queensland, Blak Social has curated a sharp line-up of...</p>
<p><a href="/event/open-air-saturdaze-with-blak-social/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Open Air: Emily Wurramara in concert with Andrea Kirwin</title>
		<link>/event/open-air-hinterland-emily-wurramara-in-concert-with-andrea-kirwin/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 05:23:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=1942</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Celebrating several of the Sunshine Coast’s regional hinterland towns, Open Air presents a Hinterland series of live music performances featuring some of Australia’s most loved musicians. EMILY WURRAMARA  Originating from Groote Eylandt in the Northern Territory, Emily is an AIR award-winning and ARIA-nominated artist. In 2018 she released the critically acclaimed album Milyakburra, educating and &#8230; <a href="/event/open-air-hinterland-emily-wurramara-in-concert-with-andrea-kirwin/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Celebrating several of the Sunshine Coast&rsquo;s regional hinterland towns, Open Air presents a Hinterland series of live music performances featuring some of Australia&rsquo;s most loved musicians. EMILY WURRAMARA Originating from Groote Eylandt in the Northern Territory, Emily is an AIR award-winning and ARIA-nominated artist. In 2018 she released the critically acclaimed album Milyakburra...</p>
<p><a href="/event/open-air-hinterland-emily-wurramara-in-concert-with-andrea-kirwin/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Babushka in Right to Party</title>
		<link>/event/babushka-kids-right-to-party/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 03:56:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=1919</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[School of Rock meets Beastie Boys and the Spice Girls in this rebellious party playlist.  A high energy cabaret for kids, featuring rebellious music, vocal acrobatics and a whole lotta mischief &#8211; spike your mohawk and fight for your right to party!   After performing to rapturous applause at Adelaide Fringe Festival and Queensland Cabaret Festival, &#8230; <a href="/event/babushka-kids-right-to-party/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>School of Rock meets Beastie Boys and the Spice Girls in this rebellious party playlist. A high energy cabaret for kids, featuring rebellious music, vocal acrobatics and a whole lotta mischief &ndash; spike your mohawk and fight for your right to party! After performing to rapturous applause at Adelaide Fringe Festival and Queensland Cabaret Festival, award-winning group Babushka has cooked up their...</p>
<p><a href="/event/babushka-kids-right-to-party/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Everybody Roar! The Best of Justine Clarke</title>
		<link>/event/everybody-roar-the-best-of-justine-clarke/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 03:47:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=1914</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Iconic entertainer &#8211; Justine Clarke (Play School) &#8211; and her band bring all her favourites to this special set, as Justine invites you to join in the fun for a sing and a dance.   Having recently released her “best of” album, Everybody Roar!, Justine and her three-piece band will groove their way through classics like &#8230; <a href="/event/everybody-roar-the-best-of-justine-clarke/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Iconic entertainer &ndash; Justine Clarke (Play School) &ndash; and her band bring all her favourites to this special set, as Justine invites you to join in the fun for a sing and a dance. Having recently released her &ldquo;best of&rdquo; album, Everybody Roar!, Justine and her three-piece band will groove their way through classics like &lsquo;Watermelon&rsquo;, &lsquo;I Like to Sing&rsquo; and &lsquo;Dinosaur Roar&rsquo;, as well as new hits like...</p>
<p><a href="/event/everybody-roar-the-best-of-justine-clarke/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>DÉ SAINT. + the Metro Collective</title>
		<link>/event/de-saint-the-metro-collective/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 03:11:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=1893</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Join one of Australia’s leading electronic artists in the gardens of the Wonderland Spiegeltent for afternoons and evenings of music and good times for the whole family.   DÉ SAINT. will be curating the Horizon Festival 2022’s Garden Soundscape with her selection of Qld’s best DJs. This is her Metro Collective: Friday 26 Aug / Stevie &#8230; <a href="/event/de-saint-the-metro-collective/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Join one of Australia&rsquo;s leading electronic artists in the gardens of the Wonderland Spiegeltent for afternoons and evenings of music and good times for the whole family. D&Eacute; SAINT. will be curating the Horizon Festival 2022&rsquo;s Garden Soundscape with her selection of Qld&rsquo;s best DJs. This is her Metro Collective: Friday 26 Aug / Stevie G / 5.30-7.30pm Saturday 27 Aug / Tilly Saunders /</p>
<p><a href="/event/de-saint-the-metro-collective/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
