<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>First Nations &#8211; Horizon Festival | Sunshine Coast</title>
	<atom:link href="/news/whats-on/category/first-nations/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Presenting 10 days and nights of visual art, music, theatre, dance, words + ideas, film and creative workshops; inspired by the stories and beauty of the Sunshine Coast.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 00:10:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Country Is Calling</title>
		<link>/event/country-is-calling/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 00:40:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=2058</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Country is Calling is a visual art exhibition that celebrates the work and stories of the Jinibara people; the Traditional Custodians of the mountains, valleys and hinterlands of the Sunshine Coast.    Curated by prominent Jinibara artist Jason Murphy, the exhibition explores the intricate connection between people and place. The four featured Jinibara artists — Jason &#8230; <a href="/event/country-is-calling/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Country is Calling is a visual art exhibition that celebrates the work and stories of the Jinibara people; the Traditional Custodians of the mountains, valleys and hinterlands of the Sunshine Coast. Curated by prominent Jinibara artist Jason Murphy, the exhibition explores the intricate connection between people and place. The four featured Jinibara artists &mdash; Jason Murphy, Caitlin Murphy...</p>
<p><a href="/event/country-is-calling/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Kabi Kabi Connections</title>
		<link>/event/kabi-kabi-connections-2/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 00:12:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=2037</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Kabi Kabi Connections is the union between time immemorial and the ephemeral, where sacred ways of knowing and being meet new technologies and the natural environment.    Curated by knowledge keeper and artist, Helena Gulash and interdisciplinary artist James Muller, this immersive and meditative work illuminates the waters of the Maroochy River with the work &#8230; <a href="/event/kabi-kabi-connections-2/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Kabi Kabi Connections is the union between time immemorial and the ephemeral, where sacred ways of knowing and being meet new technologies and the natural environment. Curated by knowledge keeper and artist, Helena Gulash and interdisciplinary artist James Muller, this immersive and meditative work illuminates the waters of the Maroochy River with the work of Traditional Custodians and visual arts...</p>
<p><a href="/event/kabi-kabi-connections-2/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Listen more not spoken for</title>
		<link>/event/listen-more-not-spoken-for/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 23:58:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=2033</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Have you ever had a conversation with country? If you listen carefully, can you hear her way of speaking with us? Immerse in the sounds of children and country hearing each other. These listening walks have been created by a team of Jarjums (Indigenous children) in collaboration with Quandamooka artist Libby Harward, their older siblings &#8230; <a href="/event/listen-more-not-spoken-for/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Have you ever had a conversation with country? If you listen carefully, can you hear her way of speaking with us? Immerse in the sounds of children and country hearing each other. These listening walks have been created by a team of Jarjums (Indigenous children) in collaboration with Quandamooka artist Libby Harward, their older siblings and our Mother Earth. The Jarjums and Libby will also...</p>
<p><a href="/event/listen-more-not-spoken-for/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Guyu and Friend Mr Pelican</title>
		<link>/event/guyu-and-friend-mr-pelican/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 06:39:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=1973</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A children’s book by Aunty Hope (Dr Hope O’Chin) that tells the Dreamtime story of a boy called Guyu and his friend, Mr Pelican. Watch a film of Aunty Hope reading the book, explore Kabi-Kabi language through the accompanying activity booklet. There will be Guyu and Friend Mr Pelican books available to take home. Guyu &#8230; <a href="/event/guyu-and-friend-mr-pelican/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A children&rsquo;s book by Aunty Hope (Dr Hope O&rsquo;Chin) that tells the Dreamtime story of a boy called Guyu and his friend, Mr Pelican. Watch a film of Aunty Hope reading the book, explore Kabi-Kabi language through the accompanying activity booklet. There will be Guyu and Friend Mr Pelican books available to take home. Guyu and Friend Mr Pelican is one of the selected Homegrown projects to appear in the...</p>
<p><a href="/event/guyu-and-friend-mr-pelican/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Open Air: Yirinda</title>
		<link>/event/open-air-yirinda/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 06:19:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=1968</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[From hidden lakes to ocean-scapes, Open Air is a vivid collision of music and place. Fast becoming an essential experience for locals and visitors alike, this intimate outdoor concert series features some of Australia’s most innovative musicians set against the Sunshine Coast’s spectacular natural environment.  Butchulla Songman Fred Leone and internationally acclaimed composer/multi-instrumentalist Samuel Pankhurst &#8230; <a href="/event/open-air-yirinda/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From hidden lakes to ocean-scapes, Open Air is a vivid collision of music and place. Fast becoming an essential experience for locals and visitors alike, this intimate outdoor concert series features some of Australia&rsquo;s most innovative musicians set against the Sunshine Coast&rsquo;s spectacular natural environment. Butchulla Songman Fred Leone and internationally acclaimed composer/</p>
<p><a href="/event/open-air-yirinda/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Open Air: Cloe Terare</title>
		<link>/event/open-air-cloe-terrare/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 06:09:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=1962</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[From hidden lakes to ocean-scapes, Open Air is a vivid collision of music and place. Fast becoming an essential experience for locals and visitors alike, this intimate outdoor concert series features some of Australia’s most innovative musicians set against the Sunshine Coast’s spectacular natural environment.  Her Debut EP Burn Book (2018-2021) spawned singles that were &#8230; <a href="/event/open-air-cloe-terrare/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From hidden lakes to ocean-scapes, Open Air is a vivid collision of music and place. Fast becoming an essential experience for locals and visitors alike, this intimate outdoor concert series features some of Australia&rsquo;s most innovative musicians set against the Sunshine Coast&rsquo;s spectacular natural environment. Her Debut EP Burn Book (2018-2021) spawned singles that were added to Triple J...</p>
<p><a href="/event/open-air-cloe-terrare/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Open Air: Saturdaze with Blak Social</title>
		<link>/event/open-air-saturdaze-with-blak-social/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 05:38:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=1947</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Celebrating several of the Sunshine Coast’s regional hinterland towns. Open Air presents a Hinterland series of live music performances featuring some of Australia’s most loved musicians. First Nations Artists bring good vibes and big ancestor energy to all they create. Leaders in the cultural resurgence of Indigenous peoples across South East Queensland, Blak Social has curated &#8230; <a href="/event/open-air-saturdaze-with-blak-social/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Celebrating several of the Sunshine Coast&rsquo;s regional hinterland towns. Open Air presents a Hinterland series of live music performances featuring some of Australia&rsquo;s most loved musicians. First Nations Artists bring good vibes and big ancestor energy to all they create. Leaders in the cultural resurgence of Indigenous peoples across South East Queensland, Blak Social has curated a sharp line-up of...</p>
<p><a href="/event/open-air-saturdaze-with-blak-social/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Open Air: Emily Wurramara in concert with Andrea Kirwin</title>
		<link>/event/open-air-hinterland-emily-wurramara-in-concert-with-andrea-kirwin/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 05:23:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=1942</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Celebrating several of the Sunshine Coast’s regional hinterland towns, Open Air presents a Hinterland series of live music performances featuring some of Australia’s most loved musicians. EMILY WURRAMARA  Originating from Groote Eylandt in the Northern Territory, Emily is an AIR award-winning and ARIA-nominated artist. In 2018 she released the critically acclaimed album Milyakburra, educating and &#8230; <a href="/event/open-air-hinterland-emily-wurramara-in-concert-with-andrea-kirwin/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Celebrating several of the Sunshine Coast&rsquo;s regional hinterland towns, Open Air presents a Hinterland series of live music performances featuring some of Australia&rsquo;s most loved musicians. EMILY WURRAMARA Originating from Groote Eylandt in the Northern Territory, Emily is an AIR award-winning and ARIA-nominated artist. In 2018 she released the critically acclaimed album Milyakburra...</p>
<p><a href="/event/open-air-hinterland-emily-wurramara-in-concert-with-andrea-kirwin/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Creative Bubs with New Dreaming Art</title>
		<link>/event/creative-bubs-with-new-dreaming-art/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 05:09:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=1936</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A chance for parents, grandparents, aunties and uncles to connect with their youngest ones. New Dreaming Art and Didgeridoo Music Therapy share their cultural history in a safe and creative space, teaching you and bub to make art that tells your own family’s story.  Enjoy the beautiful sounds of the Yidaki (didgeridoo) with Caleb while &#8230; <a href="/event/creative-bubs-with-new-dreaming-art/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A chance for parents, grandparents, aunties and uncles to connect with their youngest ones. New Dreaming Art and Didgeridoo Music Therapy share their cultural history in a safe and creative space, teaching you and bub to make art that tells your own family&rsquo;s story. Enjoy the beautiful sounds of the Yidaki (didgeridoo) with Caleb while expressing yourself through art with Nikita.</p>
<p><a href="/event/creative-bubs-with-new-dreaming-art/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Steven Oliver: Bigger &#038; Blacker</title>
		<link>/event/steven-oliver-bigger-blacker/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 02:20:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=1870</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[&#8216;What&#8217;s this then sl*t?&#8217;   You might know Steven Oliver from being sexy on ABC&#8217;s Black Comedy. Or perhaps from hosting Faboriginal on SBS. But his talents don&#8217;t end there; get ready for a bit of a rap, a bit of a sing, a bit of a tap and a lot of shaking his ring.   Bigger &#8230; <a href="/event/steven-oliver-bigger-blacker/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&lsquo;What&rsquo;s this then sl*t?&rsquo; You might know Steven Oliver from being sexy on ABC&rsquo;s Black Comedy. Or perhaps from hosting Faboriginal on SBS. But his talents don&rsquo;t end there; get ready for a bit of a rap, a bit of a sing, a bit of a tap and a lot of shaking his ring. Bigger &amp; Blacker has been described by Sydney Morning Herald as a &lsquo;tour de force&rsquo; comedy cabaret and is guaranteed to get you laughing...</p>
<p><a href="/event/steven-oliver-bigger-blacker/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
