<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Words + Ideas &#8211; Horizon Festival | Sunshine Coast</title>
	<atom:link href="/news/whats-on/category/words-ideas/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Presenting 10 days and nights of visual art, music, theatre, dance, words + ideas, film and creative workshops; inspired by the stories and beauty of the Sunshine Coast.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 06:05:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Storytellers Festival + Workshops</title>
		<link>/event/storytellers-festival-workshops/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 04:17:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=3050</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Sunshine Coast Libraries is hosting the coast&#8217;s biggest combined book launch at Beerwah. The Sunshine Coast is home to an abundance of exceptional literary talent. Libraries are bringing together writers, readers and creatives to share our love of books and support our local authors.  The Storytellers Festival 2022 offers the opportunity to meet and mingle &#8230; <a href="/event/storytellers-festival-workshops/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Sunshine Coast Libraries is hosting the coast&rsquo;s biggest combined book launch at Beerwah. The Sunshine Coast is home to an abundance of exceptional literary talent. Libraries are bringing together writers, readers and creatives to share our love of books and support our local authors. The Storytellers Festival 2022 offers the opportunity to meet and mingle with successful local authors...</p>
<p><a href="/event/storytellers-festival-workshops/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Critical Light: Industry Night</title>
		<link>/event/critical-light-industry-night/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 06:01:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=2341</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Public Discussion Horizon Festival sets out to ignite ideas and fuel the cultural vibrancy of our region through artistic experiences. As part of the Critical Light journey Liz Burcham, President of the SCCA, leads a discussion with Hannah Clissold, Ruby Donohoe, John Harvey and Libby Harward on the festivals value to our region. Ticket price includes &#8230; <a href="/event/critical-light-industry-night/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Horizon Festival sets out to ignite ideas and fuel the cultural vibrancy of our region through artistic experiences. As part of the Critical Light journey Liz Burcham, President of the SCCA, leads a discussion with Hannah Clissold, Ruby Donohoe, John Harvey and Libby Harward on the festivals value to our region. Ticket price includes a drink on arrival and entry to Homegrown: Eddie Ray &mdash; Silence...</p>
<p><a href="/event/critical-light-industry-night/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Critical Light</title>
		<link>/event/critical-light/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 03:48:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=2126</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Twelve artists journey across Horizon Festival with Provocateur, Brian Lucas — artist, educator and researcher — to shine a critical light on the program through interpretation and contextualisation, whilst engaging in rigorous discussion. About Brian Lucas Brian Lucas is a Brisbane-based performer, choreographer, director, teacher, writer and arts-advocate whose career spans almost 40 years. Trained &#8230; <a href="/event/critical-light/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Twelve artists journey across Horizon Festival with Provocateur, Brian Lucas &mdash; artist, educator and researcher &mdash; to shine a critical light on the program through interpretation and contextualisation, whilst engaging in rigorous discussion. About Brian Lucas Brian Lucas is a Brisbane-based performer, choreographer, director, teacher, writer and arts-advocate whose career spans almost 40 years.</p>
<p><a href="/event/critical-light/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Field Trip</title>
		<link>/event/field-trip/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 03:23:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=2115</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Field Trip is an experimental national research symposium featuring creative practice at the intersection of art, science, technology and the environment.  In 2022, Field Trip responds to theme of Planetary Health with a series of transient experiences including walking research panels, interactive installations and environmental immersions across the Sunshine Coast. The event will explore the &#8230; <a href="/event/field-trip/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Field Trip is an experimental national research symposium featuring creative practice at the intersection of art, science, technology and the environment. In 2022, Field Trip responds to theme of Planetary Health with a series of transient experiences including walking research panels, interactive installations and environmental immersions across the Sunshine Coast. The event will explore the...</p>
<p><a href="/event/field-trip/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
