<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Visual Art &#8211; Horizon Festival | Sunshine Coast</title>
	<atom:link href="/news/whats-on/category/visual-art/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Presenting 10 days and nights of visual art, music, theatre, dance, words + ideas, film and creative workshops; inspired by the stories and beauty of the Sunshine Coast.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 22:45:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>ReCONNECT</title>
		<link>/event/reconnect/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 04:39:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=2153</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[To accompany her exhibition The C Word, Kim Schoenberger will be hosting a two-hour experimental workshop that explores the notion of the Self through personal identity and art making. Beginning with a series of short hands-on loosening up exercises, this workshop aims to unlock pathways into the realm of creativity through the use of collage, textiles and wire armature &#8230; <a href="/event/reconnect/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>To accompany her exhibition The C Word, Kim Schoenberger will be hosting a two-hour experimental workshop that explores the notion of the Self through personal identity and art making. Beginning with a series of short hands-on loosening up exercises, this workshop aims to unlock pathways into the realm of creativity through the use of collage, textiles and wire armature sculpture.</p>
<p><a href="/event/reconnect/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Clay with Robert Natoli</title>
		<link>/event/clay-with-robert-natoli/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 04:31:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=2146</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Join expert artist, potter, painter and educator, Robert Natoli for a hands-on ceramics workshop and conversation. Bring your own wine, dig your hands into some clay and hear first-hand about Robert’s artistic process. Guests will get an expert, uniquely personal lesson in ceramic hand-building techniques from one of the Coast’s leading artists and educators at one of his resident &#8230; <a href="/event/clay-with-robert-natoli/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Join expert artist, potter, painter and educator, Robert Natoli for a hands-on ceramics workshop and conversation. Bring your own wine, dig your hands into some clay and hear first-hand about Robert&rsquo;s artistic process. Guests will get an expert, uniquely personal lesson in ceramic hand-building techniques from one of the Coast&rsquo;s leading artists and educators at one of his resident studios &ndash; The...</p>
<p><a href="/event/clay-with-robert-natoli/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Risograph printing with the Sunshine Press</title>
		<link>/event/risography-with-the-sunshine-press/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 04:18:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=2141</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Attention: Talented High School Visual Artists. Horizon Festival and The Sunshine Press are partnering to offer a free, full day workshop in the art of Risograph Printing.  The Sunshine Press are offering a small group of young Sunshine Coast Visual Artists the opportunity to learn an old art form that’s finding new life — Risograph &#8230; <a href="/event/risography-with-the-sunshine-press/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Attention: Talented High School Visual Artists. Horizon Festival and The Sunshine Press are partnering to offer a free, full day workshop in the art of Risograph Printing. The Sunshine Press are offering a small group of young Sunshine Coast Visual Artists the opportunity to learn an old art form that&rsquo;s finding new life &mdash; Risograph Printing. Applications for high school-aged artists are now open.</p>
<p><a href="/event/risography-with-the-sunshine-press/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Collage with The Butiner</title>
		<link>/event/collage-with-the-butiner/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 04:05:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=2134</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Butiner self-describes as a collage artist, flower lover, and story teller. Bring your own wine, as you create and learn with The Butiner, Peta O’Hara, in her studio, and hear about her process in this rare collage workshop.  Using identical imagery and materials, guests will create deeply originally collage postcards inspired by their own &#8230; <a href="/event/collage-with-the-butiner/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Butiner self-describes as a collage artist, flower lover, and story teller. Bring your own wine, as you create and learn with The Butiner, Peta O&rsquo;Hara, in her studio, and hear about her process in this rare collage workshop. Using identical imagery and materials, guests will create deeply originally collage postcards inspired by their own connection to their homes, in a uniquely personal...</p>
<p><a href="/event/collage-with-the-butiner/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Critical Light</title>
		<link>/event/critical-light/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 03:48:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=2126</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Twelve artists journey across Horizon Festival with Provocateur, Brian Lucas — artist, educator and researcher — to shine a critical light on the program through interpretation and contextualisation, whilst engaging in rigorous discussion. About Brian Lucas Brian Lucas is a Brisbane-based performer, choreographer, director, teacher, writer and arts-advocate whose career spans almost 40 years. Trained &#8230; <a href="/event/critical-light/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Twelve artists journey across Horizon Festival with Provocateur, Brian Lucas &mdash; artist, educator and researcher &mdash; to shine a critical light on the program through interpretation and contextualisation, whilst engaging in rigorous discussion. About Brian Lucas Brian Lucas is a Brisbane-based performer, choreographer, director, teacher, writer and arts-advocate whose career spans almost 40 years.</p>
<p><a href="/event/critical-light/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Country Is Calling</title>
		<link>/event/country-is-calling/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 00:40:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=2058</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Country is Calling is a visual art exhibition that celebrates the work and stories of the Jinibara people; the Traditional Custodians of the mountains, valleys and hinterlands of the Sunshine Coast.    Curated by prominent Jinibara artist Jason Murphy, the exhibition explores the intricate connection between people and place. The four featured Jinibara artists — Jason &#8230; <a href="/event/country-is-calling/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Country is Calling is a visual art exhibition that celebrates the work and stories of the Jinibara people; the Traditional Custodians of the mountains, valleys and hinterlands of the Sunshine Coast. Curated by prominent Jinibara artist Jason Murphy, the exhibition explores the intricate connection between people and place. The four featured Jinibara artists &mdash; Jason Murphy, Caitlin Murphy...</p>
<p><a href="/event/country-is-calling/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sunshine Coast Art Prize</title>
		<link>/event/sunshine-coast-art-prize-scap/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 00:26:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=2050</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Sunshine Coast Art Prize is one of the most dynamic and prestigious visual arts awards in Australia. Now in its 17th year, this premier art event attracts entries from established and emerging artists from across the nation. In 2022, we will have Ellie Buttrose, Curator, Contemporary Australian Art, QAGOMA, joining us as guest judge &#8230; <a href="/event/sunshine-coast-art-prize-scap/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Sunshine Coast Art Prize is one of the most dynamic and prestigious visual arts awards in Australia. Now in its 17th year, this premier art event attracts entries from established and emerging artists from across the nation. In 2022, we will have Ellie Buttrose, Curator, Contemporary Australian Art, QAGOMA, joining us as guest judge for the judged prize categories (Major Prize...</p>
<p><a href="/event/sunshine-coast-art-prize-scap/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Kabi Kabi Connections</title>
		<link>/event/kabi-kabi-connections-2/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 00:12:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=2037</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Kabi Kabi Connections is the union between time immemorial and the ephemeral, where sacred ways of knowing and being meet new technologies and the natural environment.    Curated by knowledge keeper and artist, Helena Gulash and interdisciplinary artist James Muller, this immersive and meditative work illuminates the waters of the Maroochy River with the work &#8230; <a href="/event/kabi-kabi-connections-2/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Kabi Kabi Connections is the union between time immemorial and the ephemeral, where sacred ways of knowing and being meet new technologies and the natural environment. Curated by knowledge keeper and artist, Helena Gulash and interdisciplinary artist James Muller, this immersive and meditative work illuminates the waters of the Maroochy River with the work of Traditional Custodians and visual arts...</p>
<p><a href="/event/kabi-kabi-connections-2/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Listen more not spoken for</title>
		<link>/event/listen-more-not-spoken-for/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 23:58:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=2033</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Have you ever had a conversation with country? If you listen carefully, can you hear her way of speaking with us? Immerse in the sounds of children and country hearing each other. These listening walks have been created by a team of Jarjums (Indigenous children) in collaboration with Quandamooka artist Libby Harward, their older siblings &#8230; <a href="/event/listen-more-not-spoken-for/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Have you ever had a conversation with country? If you listen carefully, can you hear her way of speaking with us? Immerse in the sounds of children and country hearing each other. These listening walks have been created by a team of Jarjums (Indigenous children) in collaboration with Quandamooka artist Libby Harward, their older siblings and our Mother Earth. The Jarjums and Libby will also...</p>
<p><a href="/event/listen-more-not-spoken-for/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Peter Hudson: The Mystery of Being Here</title>
		<link>/event/peter-hudson-the-mystery-of-being-here/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 23:44:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=2025</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Mystery of Being Here The Mystery of Being Here is the largest career survey of Sunshine Coast-based artist, Peter Hudson. Since the 1990s, Hudson has explored aspects of the natural world through painting and drawing. The landscape has been a constant for Hudson, particularly the Glass House Mountains and hinterland around Maleny where he resides. &#8230; <a href="/event/peter-hudson-the-mystery-of-being-here/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Mystery of Being Here The Mystery of Being Here is the largest career survey of Sunshine Coast-based artist, Peter Hudson. Since the 1990s, Hudson has explored aspects of the natural world through painting and drawing. The landscape has been a constant for Hudson, particularly the Glass House Mountains and hinterland around Maleny where he resides. The moon, ocean, fish, birds and snakes also...</p>
<p><a href="/event/peter-hudson-the-mystery-of-being-here/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
